On today's episode of the Command Center
podcast, we got how it started versus
how it's going, post free for agency,
and can you catch leprechaun Fred?
>> I can. It's a blow.
>> Happy St. Patrick's Day. We got draft
strategy. And then who is the advertised
reasoning goat?
It all starts right now.
>> Welcome to the Command Center podcast.
I'm Logan Pollson and as always we're
presented by Big Bear AI, mission ready
AI for a rapidly evolving world. And we
are in the Big Bear AI command center
studio. And happy St. Patrick's Day to
everybody. Fred, do you do anything?
>> St. Patty.
>> Fun for St. Patrick's Day.
>> Uh, St. Patty is a drinking day.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> So, I think me and Tana are going to
have to take on the local pub.
>> I might have to go.
>> You don't you like would you go to a pub
or you just go to any bar?
>> No, you want to you want to single out a
pub?
>> Yeah. Do you have uh like one that deck
for you?
>> Ashurn Pub. It's got a nice little feel
to it.
>> I'm just going to say Ashurn Pub is a
classic.
>> Ashurn Pub got some good wings.
>> Yeah, I'm saying it. You are a wing
connoisseur.
>> Listen, he going to go with a wing.
>> I'm going to go with a wing back.
>> I should be flying by now cuz I've been
eating wings all my damn life.
>> And like, so what is your criteria for
like a good wing, by the way?
>> It It varies. I hate wet wings. I can't
stand a wet wing.
>> That's gross.
>> I understand what you're saying. I like
them dry.
>> I like mines if I don't have a dry rub.
I want it fried. I want it breaded. And
if you want to add sauce to a breaded
wing, that I'm cool with it. Now, if you
just do a a naked fried wing, but as
long as it's fried well hard, and the
sauce is cooked in it, like it's not
like something that you say, "All right,
I'm going to fry these wings now. I'm
going to toss them as as wet as I can."
>> So, you don't like like the like the
teriyak?
>> I like the teriyak on it, but throw it
back on the grill or throw it back on,
you know, throw you scorched earth.
>> So, that I that's just my way of
preferring.
>> So, are you a drumstick or a flat guy?
>> I like both. I think they're equal. I
think when you have just one cuz I know
a lot of people that just like flats.
>> Yeah.
>> And and I hate ordering. Say for inance
we all go to eat, right?
>> And we all want 10 wings and you say I
want hot and I want all flats. Then when
I order mines,
>> I want hot too. But I want mix. If they
bring me out flats cuz he order flats
before me.
You see what I'm saying? And I done I've
been like something you'd be pissed
about.
>> I can't stand it. So
>> cuz you are very like I will say this
for people who don't know T. You are
very particular about your food. Oh,
very. Oh, he picky.
>> So, the idea that they would bring you
the wrong thing after someone else
ordered.
>> Bro, I was I was I was out one time and
and they brought they brought the wings
out and I think I don't know if it was I
don't know if it was both. I one of them
had flats
>> and they brought me my wings. I said,
"God, I cuss so loud.
I'VE BEEN WAITING 40 MINUTES AND YOU
BRING ME THE WRONG WINGS." WELL, I was
pissed off.
>> Oh my god.
>> Yeah, but I like both, man. And and I'm
I'm a wing guy, bro. Like I would go I
would go get on my bike.
>> I know you will.
>> I would go get a nice workout in
>> just so I can go enjoy some wings. And
and I'm going to tell you this. I know
we don't do too much advertising, but I
got to I got to mention it. I just found
a new wing spot this year cuz I was
working with another um company
>> and right across the street was Wingo.
>> And everybody told me, "Hey, go over
there, try their wings." And I've been
hooked. So
>> yeah,
>> that's my guy in there, too. He take
care of me. So I had to I'm
going
>> with that.
>> All right. I have to check it out. Yeah.
>> In addition to wings, we also like
football.
>> Football,
>> but not football, right? It's like the
soccer version.
>> Well, you know, they they have the claim
to the name the right of football.
>> And actually, they do play it with their
feet.
>> It is like the fact that we call
American football is kind of like
>> sideways, right?
>> I never looked at it as a being it
should it should be called something
different though. You see what I'm
saying?
If you didn't know the history behind
football or football,
>> you wouldn't look at it and say, "Well,
>> we doing something wrong by calling ours
football." You know what I mean?
>> Cuz I was called American tackle
football. Like that's the name of it.
Like a tackle football. But to me, we
should probably be named American tackle
rugby. It should be rugby.
>> Well, it's funny like rugby is Yeah.
Like cuz rugby is rugby,
>> but it's it's such a team. It's more for
football than
>> See, I look at rugby and I say it's
rugged, so it fits. You know what I
mean? The way they go about doing
>> play our game is violent.
>> It's not rugged, but it's violent.
>> And I'm like, I don't know a name that
you can put with it that that just kind
of describes that violence of our game.
>> It's funny cuz like I like my
father-in-law gave me a history of
football, which I was reading and it
started off as basically like an
American version of rugby. You know what
I'm saying? Like that's what it is. So
the fact that it transitioned into
football from even though its origin was
rug
>> and the only thing we do with the foot
is kick extra points and field goals.
>> Yeah, it is it is offs
>> and punt. Yeah.
>> I mean,
>> can we can we do the research? Jason, I
know you like to uh dig.
>> Can you go back as far as you can and
find out who named it football? Like
what was the reason behind it being
called football?
>> I think it was Teddy Roosevelt. That's
what I'm going to put my mind. But Teddy
had something to do with it cuz he
enjoyed it cuz they were f to cancel it
cuz people was getting what they used to
do.
>> They didn't have a face mask at one
time.
>> No, no, no. So it wasn't even that. You
know what they used to do back when
Teddy Roosevelt was the guy? So like we
would all get together like hold arms
>> and then the guy with the ball would
stand right behind us like a fourman
wedge but it was 15 people. Yeah.
>> And so we would just basically make a
wedge and then they would make a wedge
and we'd run into each other full speed.
>> Oh lord.
>> And that was the game.
>> So that was the that was the actual
wedge that we just got rid of.
>> Yeah. Neanderthal base and so people
because you think about it you get 15
bodies like you know 15 and 15 smashing
into each other like that doesn't feel
too good
>> so back then it was 15 players on
>> I think so it might have been 11 15 or
>> but this is at the times of the Ivy
Leagues run everything this is when you
didn't want to play Brown and Yale
>> the other thing that was crazy about old
football was like you could closed hands
punch someone in the face three
consecutive times so one two three
before it was a penalty
>> what
>> yes so the fourth one was the penalty so
it was a
>> neandabel It was a rug. Like I say, it
was as rugged as you can get.
>> Yeah. But we're talking about the
beautiful game, which is football,
soccer, cuz Columbia is playing France
at Northwest Stadium Sunday, March 29th
at 3 p.m. And all I know is that Mbappé
plays for France. Yeah. And that's
really like the only file I have on.
>> Well, he is the biggest I think he
>> soccer player in the world right now.
>> Current soccer player, right? Because
again, everyone would say Messi or
Ronaldo, but they're kind of retiring.
They not retiring, but the this the
writing on the wall.
>> The new guard is coming.
>> Yeah, the new guard is coming in. Wow.
And
>> is that dude?
>> The new guard. I
>> I ain't I know I ain't Adam Shandler,
but I just saw um uh Broncos has got
Wadd from the Dolphins.
>> What? Oh, they traded for him.
>> Yeah, that was crazy.
>> So, Adam Shner.
>> Well, I said I don't know.
>> Sher Sandler. I said
>> I said Chandler. I think I said
>> so it took me a minute and then you
Yeah,
>> I knew I knew I [__] THAT UP.
I said I'm thinking about Adam Sandler.
>> Hey. So
>> hey, that's that's a big move.
>> That's a big move for them cuz they did
need a like a a fast wide receiver to
compliment um
>> the the Dolphins just tearing it down to
the studs.
>> They got to though. They they were in a
bad way.
>> Now y'all can see why I ain't never been
a Dolphin fan. They can't get right.
>> Hey, they just tearing IT DOWN TO THE
STUDS. NO, I JUST DON'T. HEY, it
happens.
>> Yeah. So, got the soccer game.
>> Yeah.
>> 29th, 3 p.m.
>> Did you want to talk about some of the
food that's being served today?
>> Yes, I did. So, they've got empatas.
>> They got papas fras. They've got
>> papas fras.
>> Papas fras.
>> What is those? Fritos with chili.
>> It's French fries.
>> French fries.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Papa Fritos.
>> So, it's regular French fries.
>> Yeah, I guess. So, that's like the like
So, what I the Spanish from high school
is pretty limited. But what I do
remember
>> we in the same boat is Papa. feel bad
>> because like that was French fries. So
you can go to lunch line and order like
>> paprika. I literally I literally got out
of my Spanish 2 class
>> just cuz I'm like you know what I give
up. I I got to find another way to
graduate. The lady put me back in her
class. I would literally go get my
syllabus and and I knew I just got out
of the class a couple of days ago. So
I'm going to my new class. I sit down.
He's like, "We don't have you in here."
I'm like, "No, I just got out. I JUST
GOT THIS CLASS." I go back to my
counselor like someone put you back in
Spanish, too. the damn teacher kept
putting me back in her class cuz she
wanted to work with me and I'm like no I
give up
>> your name Santana she like that and that
was the problem. So the problem was any
time even when I was in high school that
all the Spanish teachers I don't know if
they kind of found a way of liking me
because of my name but they would pick
on me basically I felt I feel I was
being picked on because of my name. They
would always ask me questions because of
my name being Santana. So all I hear is
Senñor Santana
and I'm sitting up there like, "Okay,
what are you asking?" And they ask me
something in Spanish and I'm like, "No."
>> Yeah, I don't know.
>> And I'm asking somebody else what you
said.
>> Yeah, that's funny.
>> That's funny. Um, so yeah, we got the
game coming up. They've got like, you
know, food there that'll be a little bit
different. So, make sure you check it
out. I think Tana, you said you went to
a game. You said it was incredible.
>> I actually did a coin toss.
>> That's right. You said
>> did a corn.
>> So, you said it was amazing, though.
>> It was amazing.
>> So, if you got time,
>> first time ever. Soccer is just like
hockey until you see it in person.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> The the the screen doesn't do anything
for it. Like one thing about football
that make it so good for TV, it fits on
that screen. The drama, you can feel it.
You can feel the fans.
>> A hockey game SITTING ON THAT ICE RIGHT
THERE. BOY, YOU TALKING about action,
how big they are, how fast they are, and
how quick they substitute like throws me
off in in hockey. Like they in and out
of there.
>> Yeah. You know, you know, we grew up in
different areas growing up and so I
think predominantly in our neighborhoods
it was football, basketball
>> and my kids their neighborhood, they're
around a lot of Spanish guys. So their
friends are all soccer players. So I
used to ask my oldest son one time like
cuz he was into he would play on the
video game. I'm like, "Do you even know
what you're playing?" He's like, "Yeah,
I love to play it." Played a lot in PE.
I play it after school with my friends.
And I'm like, he basically showed me,
>> you know, taught me about the game. And
so when I finally got a chance to kind
of like pay attention, especially we
used to we used to have a show when I
was with 106. We used to do it at the
bar out there right across from Rose
Bar. What the uh little bar name is
across from Rose Bar down in um what is
that little area? Um
>> I know exactly you're talking about off
Connecticut.
>> Yeah, it's a little bar. But anyway,
when the soccer game is on, it's lit in
there. And we were doing a show at the
same time a soccer game was on.
>> And you can't do nothing but sit there
and participate. you going back, you
watching them
>> tearing their wings up. It was just it's
a good atmosphere even when you're not
at the game. So, no, it's interesting,
man. And if you never like myself played
it, it's something it's something fun to
watch.
>> Ted Ted Lasso helped me really take on
soccer.
>> Well, I think to your point though, like
soccer in person,
>> it's better.
>> It's different. Yeah, because like the
thing with soccer is I got to zoom so
far. Like hockeyy's too fast, it doesn't
show up on the screen. Soccer's so
zoomed out, it feels slow.
>> Yes.
>> But when you're in person, you feel
>> the speed of the game.
>> Being Think about it though. We play
football, the American football, the
running that we do is nowhere near what
the soccer players do.
>> They don't ever stop running.
>> They don't come off the field.
>> They don't stop running,
>> bro. They run. So, and I'm sitting there
saying to myself, that's why I said,
"Yeah, I picked the right sport."
Because it's knowing, you know,
>> you would have been a great soccer
player,
>> bro. that running. Oh my god.
>> They didn't just put you up there at
forward. We just like a nice direction.
>> Let him burn straight through it. Just
just run straight through.
>> Just one touch, one shot. Give it a go.
>> Just lead him.
>> Kick it out there. Lead and let him go
chase the ball.
>> Go chase the ball.
>> That would have been excellent. But so
that's soccer. Make sure you check the
game out. But in the meantime, we're
going to talk about football because
that's why you guys are here. And so
we're going to do a segment called How
It Started Versus How It's Going.
powered by Big Bear AI, mission ready AI
for a rapidly evolving world. Just
dropped my pen. And so now we're gonna
talk about who is here for the different
positions. We're gonna start with
offense and we're going to talk about
the new additions and what that means.
So let's start with the offensive line.
This is a fun group to talk about
because we've obviously got Larry Tonsel
extended, Josh Connelly, young guy. Sam
Cosby, I think if he's not coming off
that injury is like borderline pro bowl
player.
>> Oh, most definitely. He and he healthy
right now. That's all that matters. And
then we resigned Nick Aliggretti and
Andrew Wy which is awesome because those
guys I think are excellent death pieces.
And then we're able to kind of resign
Chris Paul as well. Yeah. So kind of get
the band back together for specifically.
>> Yeah. Got the band back together. You
want to talk about cohesiveness. These
guys know how to play off of each other
through each other. They know how to
play like these guys have a lot of
football played between them. And if you
got that group cohesive, that just says
everything for Jedi 5, for the running
game and for the passing game because
these guys are one healthy, two, what we
always say about I always say about
them.
>> Offensive line is a boy band.
>> Yeah.
>> I need that boy band. They got to be in
sync.
>> They got to be in sync. All right. So,
what I'm telling you this, you can't get
no more in sync than this. Yeah. All
right. They these guys been with each
other. Well, you get a you get a you get
a new kid on the block that's trying to
be in sync with the Backstreet Boys.
That's how I look at them.
>> OKAY. YOU WANT TO ONE UP ME IS WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO. NO, BUT I'm just being real.
So, so no, I'm just saying when you look
at these guys, you got winners. You got
Aligra, you got WY. These guys come from
winning, you know, championship
football. They've been here long enough
to be now, you know, the nucleus of them
being around this team. They have taught
these other guys, you know, the guys
that play the side, you know, the
Cosmies, the, you know, Josh Connelly,
these guys how how we have to play to
win. You know what I mean? Last year, if
you look at our team, probably one of
the bright spots of our offense was the
offensive line. So, when you see these
guys all being resigned, you get a guy
like Chris Paul who no one knew about
Chris Paul until last year. We had Chris
Paul, we kind of always, you know, what
he's going to do. And then last year you
say he made it hard for Coleman to even
be watch and play a position that they
basically say this is what he fits
better, you know, in our system. So I
love the fact that we've got all these
guys signed and resigned and extended,
whatever you want to call it. But also
just whoever we bring in behind these
guys, they get a chance to learn from a
group of guys that's that's going to
show them the right way.
>> You still got your Tren Scott of the
world. You still got
>> like Tren Scott.
>> You got you got your dudes. And that's
why I love this group because it ain't
no change in this group. Like they can
only get better and closer.
>> No doubt.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And I think it's
interesting like we brought Chris Paul
back cuz he had a great year last year,
but I also think like that's going to be
a competition for left guard because of
Brandon Coleman, his athleticism. So
this is a in terms of positions you
probably feel best about.
>> This it
>> it started, you know, the free agency
started. You're like, oh, you know, do
are we going to resign Larry Tonsil? Can
we get Already back? But I think this
thing is going in totally the right
direction.
>> No, most definitely. I still ain't did
the Connelly challenge.
>> You haven't?
>> That still can't do it.
>> No. No. I'm good now.
>> Feet. Knees.
>> Boy, we don't want to hit you. You know
what? I think you take a page out of
Trump book, but we ain't going TO GET TO
THAT.
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU NOW. My feet.
>> My knees feel good.
>> I just like to see you just get up off
the ground. No. No. Just sit just stand
up. Just get on camera. Just stand up
off the ground.
>> What you mean?
>> Yeah. Just like get So, sit sit sit on
your butt. Sit on your butt right here
and then just stand up off the ground.
>> Yeah. Get up now. Get up.
Okay. All right. Okay. That's better.
That's better than I thought.
>> What you thought it was going to be?
>> I thought I was going to be like, "Oh,
that old man."
>> Oh, you got a little bit.
>> You going to tell her the old No, I've
been swimming. You know, my daughter,
YOU KNOW, MY DAUGHTER GOING THE LIFETIME
with Hey, I be in there with her. She be
working me to death.
>> So, are you going to be able to do the
Connorly challenge, I think, is the
question? Yeah, I can.
>> I'm feeling good.
>> All right. Well, we'll have to get that
on camera at some point.
>> All right.
>> I can't do it. So, I don't I doubt
>> Dude, you could for sure do it.
>> You can do it. My knee been acting up,
man. I been nagging the last three
weeks. I can't do it, man.
>> Anyway,
>> 46 46 has done something to me.
>> All right, let's so talk. So, the other
position group, which is really
exciting, is the tight end group. So, we
got John Bates in terms of how it
started.
>> Bates Motel,
>> Ben Sinnet, Coulson Yanov. I think
that's a solid group.
>> Solid. You know, I've been liking that
Yank out for a minute. I know it's just
something about the kid, man.
>> Boy,
>> that ain't the reason, but
>> but what I'm saying is he he got that
>> his athletic profile to me is is one
that I look at and be like, "Hey, this
this guy can be something."
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I I agree. And so, like
you if if we had to play a game with
that, you feel good about it, right? I
think Senate with this David Blau
offense is going to be better. Bates is
going to be awesome in this. Yank off
kind of an expanding role. But then you
go sign my man Chica Conquo, right? And
when you look at
>> Say the last name again.
>> Cha Conquo.
>> A Kunquo.
>> Aqua.
>> All right.
>> Yeah. So you go sign him and I went
watched all of his plays, all of his
targets.
>> Yeah.
>> Dude's a ball player, man. He's a ball
player.
>> He's a yaxster.
>> Y.
>> He's a yaxster. He's a guy get the ball
in my hand. He can run around people. He
can run through people. He can run over
people. like he is one of those guys,
get me the rock, I'll do the rest type
of tight end. And I like that. And he's
a guy that can get up the hashes. He he
can pretty much do everything.
>> Yeah, he's one of those guys, too, when
you look at it cuz I saw a few teams do
it last year.
>> They had those tight ends where they can
be Hbacks, you know, we can do we can
run the ball with him at time. We can
give him reverses. We can give him slip
screens. He has that body type. He fits
that mo. And then when you have like I
was just talking about this off air when
you have Bates Senate and I forgot about
Yanko. I forgot how much he meant to us
last year on both both sides special
teams and offense.
>> They all have different kind of body
types and I think you can say attributes
that that come with their game. They do.
>> So one of the things that will be
something that I pay close attention to
is how how caught up we get them when it
comes to
>> not saying that okay when he's in the
game he's only in the game for this. You
see what I'm saying? That's going to be
one of the things that you got to look
at cuz, you know, teams are going to
basically scout the crap out of you and
say, "Okay, when is he coming in? Is he
coming?"
>> Yeah. When they see baits, they going
alert.
>> Bingo. So, so I want I I'm going to be
interested in just seeing how well he
blocks, how well he gets in there and
get in that three, you know, technique
and then go out there and and and put
that right on somebody.
>> I will say this about him, like again,
he's not a killer. Yeah. Right. He's not
a killer in the run game because he's a
smaller guy, right? He's like 20. I
think he's 30, but he's willing.
>> He's very willing. And I think when you
when you see him block safeties, when
you see him block corners, when you see
him block linebackers and D lineman's a
little bit hit or miss, he'll wear those
guys out now. He wants to be good at
that. He wants to finish. And to me, if
you're urgent at that and you want to
finish, like we can win with that. You
know, you can crack a safety, we can
like play fullback, lean up on a
linebacker. I will say the other thing,
too, he's a little stiff. So, a little
bit different than like Zack Herz in
terms of how he's going to win cuz he's
he's like, I'm fast and explosive. I'm
going to win that way and a little bit
of a body catcher, but I think he's a
heck of a football player. And I think
you were talking about usage and tells
like I think you get in a 13 personnel,
have John play the Y, um, uh, Ben play
the F and then he would play like the Z
receivers
and he can run some of that route tree
now and that would be a great way to get
good matchups out of that personnel
grouping moving forward. All right, this
Okay, so tight end I'm excited about
because they've, you know, all the guys,
the guys last year are good.
Addition of Chig is really exciting. The
one that I have like kind of the most
questions about still even post free for
agency is DB. And we're going to break
this up into two. We're gonna do corners
and safety. So yeah, at corner you got
Trey Amos, Mikey Sanders, and Amique
Robertson. So it so
>> going good like the young talent there,
right? And then you make the addition of
Amique Robertson who's kind of this
junkyard dog. I still think you need a
little bit of depth there in terms of
the way this thing is going.
>> I see I see where you're talking about
where you would need some some guys
behind them. probably you want to get
somebody with a little length
guy cuz you look at him meek. He's not
the biggest guy.
>> What you think? Have you watched him at
all?
>> Yes, I have.
>> What do you think about him?
>> You know how you ring somebody doorbell
and that little feisty dog come over
there. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Little scrappy
dude.
>> That's what he is.
>> Little scrappy dude.
>> He just I watch him and I had to give
him some props for this. Two times he
had to go battle Justin Jefferson all by
himself. I mean, no help.
>> And that dog stood up to the fight. And
that dog kept on fighting. So he ain't
going to ever give up. He, like I say,
feisty. And he's a better tackler. Cuz
you look at his size and you'll be like,
"Ah, he no tackler." He's a better
tackler than you think he is. He's one
of them people I say he's a jack of all
trades. He's he don't have that one
thing that stands out of I'm I'm I'm I'm
>> just heads over heel better than this
department. He's a little bit of
everything and he's scrappy as hell. So
I go to war with him. I go to war. I'm
going to tell you what, he one of them
people you will not appreciate. players
probably appreciate him more than the
people outside of football.
>> All right. Ryan Clark when Ryan played
for us.
>> Yeah, we appreciated what Ryan
>> Ryan had that thing had us all in the
right spots. But you wouldn't appreciate
Ryan if you were playing for another
team. You' be like, "No, they're just
Ryan Clark." No, like some people they
got more wealth to them than what people
want to give him props for. And I think
with with Robinson, he's one of those
guys that the locker room will feel him
more than the people outside the locker
room. Yeah, I watch them play and I mean
I appreciate just seeing I mean I think
we live in a world we live in a society
too that people hear names and people
hear they see they see uh accolades,
they see the Pro Bowls, they see the
interceptions
>> and they take away from just the work
the body of work that that goes into
just even being able to even be
considered a Pro Bowler or to have that
as as many picks. Then you we have more
guys like Amit Meek Robinson in this
league than we do
>> Patrick Certain Certain. Yeah. You see
what I'm saying? And so I'm gonna
appreciate that guy. Like I told you all
the time when y'all ask me who's one of
my favorite guys going against. I always
tell y'all the dude from Dallas Newman
because it was the whole package. It was
the guy that I know that and then he can
run with you. He got long arms. You want
to beat him every down like you still
got to work. You don't get a Deion
Sanders every play for everybody team.
You get more a Meek Robinson. So he's a
guy that showed me out the gate. You
talked about the Jefferson game. I saw
plenty of games from Detroit when they
had to play in prime time games and
those games that mattered that this guy
stood out. You know what I mean? You saw
him making play
>> in the playoff game. He got hurt the
first quarter when we played him. So
>> So like, so I love the fact that we
bring a guy like that in because it fits
what we're trying to do defensively and
it only adds to what we already have
that who I feel that you got two of the
best in the league. You know, I I love
what Trey did last year as a rookie and
Sanders is only going to get better.
>> Yeah. And everybody talking about the
yard yours sandwich game. Let me tell
you as a corner. If they throw at us
enough, we going to give up yours. I'm
I'm sorry. They're just part of it,
>> dude. We just did a drive to the draft,
our draft podcast, we did corners and
it's like you you watched, you know, I
watched a ton of film and every corner
gets beat.
>> And even if the best guy in the draft
class going to get beat, Patrick Satan
going to get beat. Like it's just it's
one of those things. It's a tough thing.
It's like an offensive lineman, you
know? Like you don't notice them
>> until they get beat. Correct. Until they
get beat. And then here go thing about
it too, especially at that corner
position, it's hard to judge some
corners cuz once you got a little name
recognition,
>> I can't really judge your play when they
don't throw at you. You see what I'm
saying? Like
>> it's like the same the thing with
Patrick saying and Riley Moss last year.
I think Riley Moss is a fine corner.
>> Yeah, but he gave up 800 yards,
>> but he gets picked on a ton.
>> Yeah, because they don't want to go over
there.
>> Yeah. So he he gets a lot of he gets a
lot of
>> It's the same way with your guy Diggs
from Dallas. when he was in Dallas,
Diggs had all the picks in
>> but he gave the most yards. You know
what I'm saying? So, you're going to get
the ball thrown on you and this is about
how many plays can you make make to make
a difference for the outcome to change.
>> Also, the other thing I wanted to bring
up and just ask you guys real quick cuz
I do think like I'm excited about the
Meek Robinson thing. I think I like like
you talked about the personality seems
like the right thing for the Commanders.
They didn't really make a lot of moves
at DB. Does this signal signal to you
that they're going to be in more base
defense with three linebackers on the
field, four linebackers on the field?
>> No. No. They just tell me they
confidence in their young talent.
>> They're good with it.
>> They're good with it and they want to
see it grow.
>> Don't they normally carry like five
corners on the roster?
>> And I'm sure we're probably not going to
say we're not through shopping in that
department cuz I like I say, I think
they going to just search for a body
type for the last guy.
>> I think they want they want a tall
corner in here. And the thing I wanted
to ask you about too, Fred, because you
would know, is like to me, I don't know
if the height length stuff is as
important because like when you watch
Minnesota, it's like we're standing at
seven, eyes on the quarterback. Yeah.
Breaking on footballs.
>> Yeah. Well, the one thing about it is
the one thing about the difference
between a tall corner and short corner
is
>> arm length. All right. When you try to
throw fade route, have you noticed I
never really got beat on a lot of fade
route. Even if I'm out of transition,
>> like even if the dude got a step on me,
>> he don't anymore. Yeah.
>> And and that's the only thing about the
the the long and the short.
>> I I don't know if you've seen this guy.
Again, he's a little bit of a niche pull
from the draft show, but his name's
Takario Davis.
>> This dude's 6'4. He's got 33 and a half
inch arms
>> and dude never gets beat on a fade. Like
even though he's not like the fastest
guy, he just is so like stretch arm.
Think about what I used to crab about
years ago when we had a coner here that
I felt was long, had a great wingspan,
and I'm like, if you just watch the
ball,
>> I don't care what that guy got to step
on. You throw that hand up. It's good.
>> You know what's crazy though? He's still
in the league and he just got paid
pretty good money.
>> That's what I'm saying. SO EVERYBODY SEE
WHAT I SAW.
>> Y'all talking about the sanctions.
>> But I'm saying no. Like no, no, no
flack. No, I'm not trying to throw no
shade. I'm just saying as a receiver, if
you know yourself, if you if you played
that position long enough, it's all
about leverage. That's all it is. It's
leverage, bro. You can have a step on
me, but as long as I'm there and I can
see what's going on, you ain't getting
that ball over my head. You know what
I'm saying?
>> You ain't getting it. And that's that's
the difference in that length. Like,
>> I'm going tell you this. Have you How
many times you seen Richard Sherman get
beat on the fade?
>> Just never.
>> He was notorious at that.
>> When when they had a couple steps on
him, he going to knock it down.
>> Yeah. Knock it down. run a dig right on
him.
>> Yeah,
>> you got him. You got him every time.
>> That's thing. It's like scheme is so
important. So, he's great for cover
three because you just defend the third.
>> You don't have to worry about the third
about the dig because there's a hook
player there. So, like it's
>> it's go routes and comebacks. Like
that's what you That's what he had to
defend.
>> That's what he had to defend.
>> And being and being an ex receiver, too,
that helped cuz
>> Oh, no. Yeah, he was anxious.
>> Well, dude, I remember when we played
Seattle when they were like at the peak
of their powers and it was like you'd
run these route, you know, you run
routes and you're like, I'm not running
it on a corner or a linebacker cuz the
way their coverage Yeah. dispersed. So,
it's like
>> it really has to space appropriately.
And the only reason it didn't space
appropriately is because the rush was so
good.
>> The rush was good. Plus, you had an
enforcer and Cam Chancellors taking away
the middle.
>> Their post safety, I always forget about
it.
>> Earl Earl Thomas was such
>> he was the guy
>> a beast. He was the thing that made the
whole thing go. Apparently, it was Cam
that made it go.
>> Cam was the Cam was the bone crusher and
Earl was the guy Earl was the
>> He was the guy that orchestrated
everything. He was the one put put
people in place and then he made the
plays plays as well.
>> I don't know if you remember this like
so we were watching a cut up of
Seattle's defense kind of working
through the rules with Kyle and Earl's
in the middle third so you know he's
like
>> barely on the screen on the wide copy
and they're throwing a quick game slant
to the offensive right which is to the
field. Yeah. And this dude from 20 yards
back is breaking up the pass with a hit
on a slant. And so his ability to cover
grass and arrive violently like that
dude I don't know. He doesn't get he's a
Hall of Fame guy in my opinion. He did
not get enough credit in terms of
>> I think I think later when that when
that whole defense broke up and he went
elsewhere that's where he didn't really
>> when he went to Baltimore he had lost a
step a little.
>> Yeah. You heard? But but in Seattle,
>> that boy Earl was that guy
>> was a dude.
>> Cam too. Cam, I told you. But I I tell
you, I I that's the only time I I had my
I had them tweety birds and I and they
ain't they ain't leave the whole game
>> talking about getting your you know
what, boy. Look at here. You know how
somebody and this the thing about
football cuz you see so many guys they
get hit these days and they like I'm out
of here, man. I'm gonna go ahead and
check out
>> Yeah. That boy Kale hit me and um they
got this little You watch the um what's
the show with the guy? He's a
skateboarder and he has a a comedy show
that he talks about oh spills and falls
and
>> ridiculousness. Ridiculousness.
>> So they had a they got a um they had a
word for for for a particular fall. I
think it's called the Scorpio. Scorpion
like where your feet touch your
>> So, bro, I got hit by Cam like that and
as I'm going back,
>> I knew my head was going to hit sooner
or later. I just ain't no wind. But my
but my toe touched before my head hit.
>> Hey,
>> that boy had you IN THE FULL NAIL.
>> HEY, BRO. I GOT up and it was instant.
>> Oh, just that.
>> And then it's wet out there and I'm like
And I hear somebody
>> I'm like [__] YOU.
DO IT AGAIN. LIKE but deep down inside
you ain't want no more.
>> And some my enemy was like telling to
get out the game.
>> Yeah, JUST GET OUT.
>> MY PRIDE WAS. So I'm like hell no I
ain't getting out of this game. So I'm
in a huddle
>> and Robert calling the players. I'm just
like
and I just broke I bro say [__] I'm just
look at the formation and I'm going to
run this route and I remember loafing on
a couple of routes and Kyle after like
week later Kyle like tell why you not
running this hard man I don't shouldn't
have been out there I shouldn't even
told y'all but I shouldn't have been out
there but bro that was my first time out
all the years I done played this game I
ain't never been hit like that listen
remind me of when I got ran over by
Jerome Bettis
Well, you said Jerome kept picking you
up and putting you back down.
>> His body was just so bad. I couldn't
grab I would grab his gut back. I
couldn't I couldn't get nothing down. I
like damn Jerome.
>> My goodness. All right, let's talk about
safety real quick. So, Percy Butler,
Will Harris, Quan Martin, all returning,
right? And I think the Will Harris one
is a sneaky signing.
>> I like that wheel.
>> Tyler Owens, Jeremy Reeves also. And
then you add Nick Cross
>> and all of a sudden that room feels
>> it glows.
>> Yeah, it goes. It glows.
>> It goes in a nice way, which is pretty
exciting.
>> And that's what you want cuz one thing
about Nick Cross, he's wellrounded.
>> Yeah.
>> Tackles well, coverage well,
communicates well. He's an enforcer.
Yeah.
>> All right.
>> And we got And we got a And we got a
Redskins/commander back in the house cuz
this guy grew up he grew up here and he
said that was he went to Maryland, but
he was a real fan of the
>> of the team of the franchise. So he
going to give blood, sweat, and tears in
there. I feel like you you don't feel
like that defensive back room got a big
boost. I did cuz I'm
>> No, it did get I'm saying it got a big
boost, but I'm saying does it inform
like a direction, you know, because you
don't have a lot of perimeter corners.
You got a lot of safety type bodies. So,
are you in more
>> big dime, big nickel like with these
types of players? I can say I think
that's going to work itself out cuz when
you got a guy like Tyler Owens
>> like you're going to try to find places
to work him in as a big nickel. You
going to find sometimes you like so I
just think it's not always based off
body type. I think it's just based off
certain and then you got to realize a
guy like Jeremy Reeds I think he showed
last year.
>> I think he showed that man I I want to
play some more safety. Yeah, but I look
at it too, man. You look at this and
like I said, I always throw this out
there because you have to assume what
did you see Minnesota do well? Like did
did you see some of these packages with
more safeties or did they have
>> Well, they would do it with Martellis
>> number 44.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah.
>> They would bring him down as the big
nickel.
>> Well, so like they had like the highest
base percentage in the NFL. They had a
lot of three safety. Like they just did
a lot of like kind of uncon like
everyone's playing more nickel.
>> They want to go the opposite way. They
>> went the other way. I'm just kind of
curious if like these moves indicate
that or if I'm just thinking
>> and that's why I was saying too just
just from hearing what coach said in the
presser, you know, he basically said
like there's plenty of ways to get to
what we trying to show. You know what I
mean? I don't have to line up a certain
way for you to see what I have as long
as we get there. You know what I mean?
Long as it end that way. So I'm I'm
optimistic. Whatever it is, he doing
what he's doing for a reason.
>> And I think Nick Cross again to that
point like he can basically play like
pseudo linebacker like really good
blitzer. So like to that point like
maybe he's a linebacker in some looks.
some looks
>> like an edge setting player and certain
looks. So, he he brings that skill set.
So, I don't know why DBs were in with
the offense. That's on my that's my
fault, guys. That's bad producers
because, you know, we're really
offensive players.
>> Yeah. And so, let's do uh receivers real
quick and then uh so we got Terry
McLaren resigning Luke McCaffrey, Jaylen
Lane, and then we resigned or we signed
>> Y
>> um Van Jefferson, Dei Brown, Tayen
Burks.
>> Yeah, I got to kind of size Van
Jefferson up earlier. I had an interview
with him. Check that out. Don't get
loud. taller kid than I thought he was.
>> His dad was a hell of a receiver, too.
>> His dad was a hell of a receiver.
Retired the year before me and Tana got
to the league.
>> Good coach,
>> D. And the guy, he's won the Super Bowl.
He's been with McVey. He's been part of
the offenses. Uh, and he's that type of
guy. One thing that I did notice with AP
did,
>> most of the guys that he brought in free
agency, they all come from winning teams
>> and they all got a winning pedigree. So
when you look at this, do you look at
this wide receiver group and say they're
kind of like some of the got some of the
same skill sets?
>> Well, you said something to me, Tana,
that I think is right on the money. You
said this is 2024, right? You've got
guys that are solid players, role
players, and I think in the right system
can be more than what they were in their
previous spots. Like Tayen Burks for
sure, Dami, I think when you use him
correctly, is like a vertical down the
field kind of guy. In Jacksonville,
they're trying to get him to be like a
true Z. Yeah,
>> sure. That's who he is, right? Van
Jefferson, excellent route running
nuance. Catches the football well. Not
as fast, but like there's a there's a
role for that type of guy.
>> So, I I definitely think you maybe want
to get more like athletically talented
in this room, but I think you've got all
the pieces you need and I feel pretty
good about where they're at.
>> Well, I like the maturity of Luke. I
like I'm pulling for Luke cuz I thought
Luke was hitting his stride last year.
>> You were.
>> Uh Jaylen Lane, come on. He was a rookie
last year. I think
>> he's got a big ceiling ahead.
>> Yeah, I think he can only get better.
And it ain't really his his route
running nuance. It's just concentration
on on finishing catches.
>> This this group reminds me a lot of the
2012 group where you had a committee of
guys that went out there and and that
count offense. You had Pierre, myself,
>> um Morgan, you had uh Hankerson, you had
Al. All us went out there and put up at
least 500 yards like and and it was able
to be a productive core because you had
different guys. You had a speedster. You
had a guy who can, you know, who was
also fat. You had three guys that can
run 43 44. And then you had a guy that
had had tremendous, you know, catch
radius and Morgan, he caught everything.
Big hands, tough and fast. Big old legs.
Pierre was tough and fast. I mean, you
had guys that just complimented each
other. Now look at these guys. remind me
of 2024 cuz we didn't know what that
group was going to be until we watched
that group play play together and then
they all complimented each other. They
all did something special that the next
man probably couldn't do by itself. So I
look at these guys and I say the same
thing with all that in mind. You're
still going to probably get another guy.
You're still probably going to get a
younger guy in a draft. So who knows
what you're going to bring in to add to
this this group. And I think right now
this if we had to go play today with
this group, I would be happy with this.
I feel like all these guys can can can
do a lot. You got you got Van Jefferson
who can move the chains. I saw him be
the third guy, the second guy, you know,
with the Rams. Dei had one of his best
years his last year. I was one of
scratching my head why you leave. You
know what I mean? But I understand
people want to see that payday and and
he did just that. But he's back and we
can use him the same.
>> To me, Burks, he's the guy that you talk
about different bodies. Yeah. Big guy.
Yeah.
>> You know, red zone guy, but he also
shows he can run tremendous routes. He
also can be tough. if he can be that guy
and and and and shield guys from the
ball, you know, be that big tight end
kind of body. So, I'm I'm loving what I
see. And then talking about Luke,
talking about Jaylen, these guys going
to only get better.
>> Yeah, they going to get better. I I
could add a Malachi Fields or something
to this group.
>> No, there Fields. Yeah.
>> Well, well, cuz his size Jason on
Malachi Fields. You guys love that guy.
>> Well, I just like I like his catch
radius.
>> The receiver from Notre Dame, by the
way.
>> Yeah. He He ain't He ain't the fastest
guy. No. But boy, boy, boy, he know how
to play some basketball.
>> Yeah, he does know how to play some
basketball. All right, let's talk about
running back real quick. This one is one
they need to do a little bit of work on
because Bill Crosky Merritt was the only
ones in the room when it started and
then now that it's going, they got
Rashad White, Jerome Ford, kind of two
guys that are similar in my opinion. And
then they obviously were signed Jeremy
McNicholson. So, they're all kind of
these, you know, experienced third down
pass catchers. I can say wellrounded
back like all of these guys can catch,
>> all these guys can run, all of these
guys can block. Yeah,
>> like that. That's what it is. But it's
no one guy that just going to
>> stick out to you. Now, the one thing
about Rasheed White is he could be one
of the better receiving wide rece I mean
uh running backs in the league.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And it's not like he's running
like receiver routes. He's running
stuff.
>> He running wheel routes. He running all
kinds of stuff. So, and him and Jedi 5,
they played together before. So, it's a
relationship there. And we got a lot of
that crosspollination
>> going on with some of these players that
didn't played together.
>> Yeah. Well, most definitely cuz it helps
the locker room jail that fast.
>> All right. So, we're going to do defense
here in a second, but let's pay some
bills with break one. And I will say
what
>> I got the answer to Tana's thing.
>> Football.
>> All right. This is from the Pro Football
Hall of Fame.
>> Pro Football Hall of Fame.
>> All right. Like the game itself, the
word football has uh foreign ancestors.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Trace American football back
to two European cousins. You can guess
what they are.
>> Soccer
>> and rugby. Right. Right. Those were both
called football at the time.
>> Oh, no kidding.
>> Yeah. So, uh to try and like figure out
a way to differentiate between them,
they called uh soccer or what became
soccer was called the association of
football. They shortened that to a so
which they then shortened a sock. Now we
call it soccer. Let's go.
>> So, just kept going down. Rugby, they
just cut football out and they're like,
"You're rugby now."
>> All right. So, then we adopted here in
America adopted both those games
combined, soccer and football that
turned into what we have now and we just
called it football.
>> That's cool. Yeah, that's dope.
>> So, that's how it happened.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Uh and then before you began
this, I have a kind of like a surprise
for you. Amanda's going to go get it for
you. So, our fans have been really
loving your guys competition when it
comes to the reads. Um, so we were able
to scr together a few bucks. I convinced
her of Boston.
>> So, uh, that'd be cool.
>> Right now, we have something for whoever
wins the week. You can comment. Leave a
comment on who wins the week for. We
will put next to you this trophy Amanda
is going to bring out.
>> Oh, WE GOT THIS TROPHY. Bring it on out.
So, the winner
>> and the goat
>> will get the goat command center.
Greatest of all time.
>> Find out.
Look at this thing.
>> There you go. You'll get this trophy.
>> Nice,
>> dude. Look at that.
>> Yeah. So, the winner
>> you put
>> each week we will put we will put next
to you in the background. So, you will
have it. You'll be the goat. We also
have
>> What else we got, Jason?
>> If you would like
>> the goats ride.
>> I just like the shades on that thing.
>> I know the shades on the goat.
>> Telling me something.
>> You know what? I'm going to buy
>> If you would like, you can go do that
and CC wine.
>> If you would like just to rub it in the
next time. We also have the goat chain
>> that you can also wear if you would
like.
>> Bro, this is dope.
>> So, you're the greatest of all time. It
even says on the Air Command Center
podcast for the reads here. So,
>> yeah, let me go and put that on.
>> No, don't know if anybody's putting it
on.
>> So, every week based on the comments,
someone else will be the goat and we'll
put this up there.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah, it's it's the real thing, friends.
>> Dust around here, ain't it?
>> Dust. Well, I don't I don't think you've
run won a read, have you?
>> [__] your back.
>> Sorry. I just That's what I thought. I
don't know.
>> Ain't one
of a few of them. I mean, he's been
killing it lately. So, um Jason, is that
all the fun surprises that we've got?
Yeah. Let's hand that over to Jason real
quick. That's heavy.
>> So, is this chain?
All right, let's pay some bills here
real quick. And then again, we're we're
we're playing for like hardware now,
boys.
>> Oh, no. It's it's been competition. It's
been lowkey like serious. Like our whole
schools have really been standing behind
us in this thing. UCLA has been let down
tremendously.
>> I mean, tremendously. You know what
tremendously mean? I mean, I think it's
a big deal.
>> I'm just saying, man.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Here we go.
>> Okay, here we go.
>> There you go. When the mission is
critical and readiness matters, Big
Bear.AI delivers proven AI technology
and expertise to help safeguard national
security and critical infrastructure.
This mission ready AI big bear.ai
official partner of your Washington
command.
>> Okay. Oh, dude. He's in it now. He's in
it. He wants it.
>> Look what that MAN HAD TO DO.
>> THAT BOY BORN A LITTLE BLEED. HE DON'T
KNOW HOW TO ACT.
>> Oh my god.
>> Dude, it was He was ready to go.
>> He came. He came with it.
>> Pressure's on.
>> I had to get Z in.
>> Oh my god. Boy Fred, you
Let's get it. Commander fans, your
fandom just got an upgrade. Introducing
the AAA Commander membership. MVP
membership. That is where real fans get
real perks and same trusted AAA
membership benefits. The new AAA
Commander membership provides a chance
to win game tickets, access to VIP
events and experiences, 15% off
Commander online pro shop while
providing peace of mind for Commander
fans on the road. Already aa member?
Don't sit on the sideline. upgrade your
membership or join today
ata.com/commanders.
>> Get that get that goat out of here.
>> BB and CC.
>> Get that goat out of here.
>> I want to wear that goat ch. That's what
I did. I passed it to you.
>> The goat.
>> Come on. I had to give you a little
confidence, man.
>> Yeah. Little little something.
>> Ain't no wrong with it.
>> Oh, dude. He came and I think it like
rattled Tana. Like I haven't seen Tana
that rattle in a while.
>> No. You know what it was? I was laughing
too much. I should I should have been
serious.
>> I give you. Hey, I ain't going to lie,
bro. I got to give it to you, brother.
>> There's still one more. We'll see what
happens.
>> Yeah, it just started.
>> It just first first quarter right here.
>> Yeah. Listen, we used to four quarters
and then we played here sometime. Five
>> five quarters. That's right. A lot of
times.
>> All right. So, let's do our uh let's do
how it started versus how it's going
with the defense. We'll go a little bit
quicker here cuz like I mean we've
talked about these guys a lot already
but linebacker started Jordan McGee,
Frankie Louvu, Kane Madano and then they
added or it's going to uh Leo Chanel and
I just feel like Leo Chanel is like the
perfect fit. I don't know. I don't want
to say I don't want to overhype it but
like
>> No, he is.
>> He can cover, he can run, he can play in
line, he can play edge.
>> Think Van Ginkle.
>> Yeah,
>> think Van Ginkle from Minnesota. All the
stuff that Van Ginko does. He one game I
watched him rush the passer, cover tight
ends, like play middle linebacker,
>> more more more backer to his game as
opposed to defensive line with Van
Ginkle. But yeah, that same type of
flexibility.
>> The ace in the hole.
>> He's one of those guys. I mean, he said
it itself, man. He his game is about
being violent
>> and that's what you want. You want a
linebacker that's I mean, that's one of
the things that
>> I would love to see our 54 back,
>> whatever may happen. But Bobby to me
that was he
>> you could say what you want to say about
coverage I care less when you tackle the
way Bobby been tackling these last few
years.
>> Yeah.
>> That's what I want all our linebackers
to be able to turn the film on and say
you know what this is this is the this
is the
>> this is who we need to uh I guess you
could say imitate. I want to look I want
my tackling game to look like Bobby's.
And I think when you watch uh Leo you
know I mean and and what he displayed he
he has it all. He has a package that,
you know, sometime linebackers are kind
of put into this little, I guess you
could say, yeah, a bubble where they
say, "This is what we want you to do."
Not in this game today.
>> You got to do
>> today. You got to be able to rush. You
got to be able to cover and you got to
be able to tackle. So, when you look at
what we have, that's what you have in a
guy like
>> your guy showed us a lot last year. Joy
McGee.
>> Yeah. Joy McGee.
>> Like Joy McGee. Like the question is,
can he take that big step
>> this year to say, you know what, I'm
here. I ain't going nowhere. Right. Can
he become that main fixture? Because
when I look at this thing, I I look
forward to Frankie Luvu bouncing back
because now I think he will be used
correctly the way that he was supposed
to be used. And what we going to get
from the old the old brewing? What we
going to get from
what we going to get from that old
Bruin?
>> He's got a little bit of developing to
do, but I I think it's a it's a fun
room. They've got two young guys that
I'm excited about. I think you've got
Frankie on a bounceback year, and I
think Leo Chanel, his best football is
ahead of him, right? like like when
you're going to blitz him, have him
attack cuz he was playing behind Nick
Bolton and I forget the other guy's name
in Kansas City, but kind
>> he know he was the third guy there,
right? He was the third guy. And so for
him to get a a bigger role, I think he's
ready for it.
>> Great physicality. All right, let's talk
about the defensive tackle. So this one
is interesting because I think the
started was pretty good. Don Payne,
Javon Kinlaw, Johnny Newton, and then
you bring in the return
>> of Tim Settle and I think he kind of
fits really nicely with the room of the
Mac. Hey, Tim settles. You know they
>> he actually we I almost kidding to each
other. Well, he's my he's my kids cous.
>> Oh, y'all remember you told me that.
>> Yeah, he's my kids cousin. So, like I
tell my kids all the time on they mama's
side. So, what I tell them, if you got a
pro on your mama's side and your daddy
is a pro, you got no excuses. All right.
So, the one thing I know about and Tim
is from Manasses. He's from Manasses.
And
>> I think that's fun that him and Nick
Cross are both from the area.
>> Yes. him and Nick Cross and Cheek played
at Maryland
>> also.
>> But he's from He's from Atlanta.
>> He's from Atlanta. Yeah. But I just
think when it comes to Tim Settles, he
went and found his game. You know how
sometime when you go to another team,
>> you you Yeah. You go you grow up and you
you know the best thing you can do in
the NFL is not worry about what you
don't do well. Worry about what you do
great. What's the What's the one thing
that makes you different? And his run
stopping ability makes him different.
All right. and he showed it playing and
he he went played a high a lot of
highlevel playoff games in Texas in in
Houston and and most our guys are all
highlevel playoff guys and he's one of
those guys. No, I man look when he left
us I was pissed because I felt like you
saw a guy that was getting better. Like
he was just finally getting that I guess
you can say you know how like when
you're young in the game and you're a
little wet behind the ears and you just
>> you don't know no better
>> and now you're finally getting those
repetitions and you getting out there
like that's what you saw from him here.
Like every time he got in the game he
flashed. Yeah. He did something that
just you was like okay he come around
the corner. He come around that curve.
He he he getting to know what what his
role is. And when he left, I was kind of
sad for the simple fact cuz I wanted to
see more develop and then you saw him do
that on the other, you know, other team.
And so I look at that as a guy, you
know, when Tim was here was like almost
like those high school years though that
that couple of couple of years with him
was like he was in high school, then he
went off and went to college and he
comes back now he's a pro. You know what
I mean? Now he's he's learned how to
play the game. And even or you can say
like like myself when I was in New York,
I feel like I grew up there. Like my
first year was bumpy, but second, third,
and fourth year,
>> I was able to put the reps behind my
game and to know what it takes to be a
pro. And by the time I got here, I'm
wondering why you hitting on all
cylinders because, bro, I just went
through hell, you know, trying to find
out who who I am and how to play this
game. And now I'm ready for it. So,
>> yeah. Well said. And I think the other
interesting thing is he feels like he
fits really nicely with like maybe a
weak spot of the room, like just being
that pure
>> run stop. Yeah, I'm going to go get
dirty. Like, I'm I'm going to do the
dirty work. Like, you can't have a great
defense that's led by great linebackers
unless you got great defensive linemen
keeping them clean.
>> All right. Ray Lewis made a a career out
of that. But he ain't doing that without
Sarah Gusa and the rest of them dudes
keeping them clean. That's the thing
about
>> I remember the one year when they took
Sarah Gusa and boy, he he HE GOT TOSSED
AROUND.
>> Ray Lewis said, "Hey, y'all better find
find a way. Go get somebody." That's
right. I remember that year, man.
>> Yeah. So, that's what hopefully Tim
Settle brings to this defense. And then
defensive end is maybe the most exciting
position coming out of this whole thing
right now.
>> So, obviously Dorance um resigned Dietri
Weise, John Baptist, and again that room
you're like, uh, like Dorance coming off
the ACL, Dietri coming off the injury,
John Baptist coming off the injury, like
what are we going to do here? And they
come back and they're like, "Oh, how
about Adafo? How about uh how do you say
his first name?"
Cavon
>> Cavon Chasan.
>> Okay. I thought it was Le'Veon, but
anyway, Cavon Chaon and then Charles
Amenu getting some really good starting
plus starter caliber depth there and
good depth pieces there with Charles
Amenu
>> and championship football. Championship
football. These guys playoff football.
That's what all of them got in common.
>> Yeah. And so I think we talk about roles
in this defense like Chaon can play
stand up edge. He can drop in a
coverage. Dorance Armstrong can do that
as well. a DOE man watching him and with
the Chargers I'm I'm so excited for him.
Yeah,
>> I'm so excited for what he could mean.
And then you look at Dietri Weise,
Charles Manu, the ability to play four
eye three technique, true defensive end,
have some flexibility there on pass
rushing downs.
>> I I was so excited about Dietri Weise
coming into last year, man. I Yeah, I
was like his
>> He is so strong at the point of attack.
His hands are so heavy.
>> What you call him? You call
>> just a ogre. just one eye
>> and just and just a lovely human being.
Just
>> the nicest dude you have ever been.
>> Great guy,
>> great dude, great football player. Just
everything about him, man. Like I say,
>> I talk I tell the story all the time
about being the huddle and looking at um
Logan shoes. I looked at that when he
came on SET
>> WITH THEM SIZE 18
>> THAT I SAY, "BUT DAMN BOY, that boy got
some rims on his on his ankles down
there." And he just a beautiful human
being, man.
>> Dude, man, he was dude.
>> But, you know, Charles Menu's kind of
built this like they're just big dudes,
you know, cuz I played with him in
Houston when he was a rookie, you know,
so he's got 36 inch arms.
>> See, we keep forgetting how young you
really You just look old. You ain't
really that old.
>> Yep.
>> I just I just got an I'm an old old soul
and an old face. It's just a tough deal
for me. But that's the defensive guys
right there. And again, really excited
about that group. We've talked about
them a lot. So, if you want to hear us
more in-depth analysis, you can check
back on our last podcast. But in the
meantime, let's pay some break uh pay
some bills and we'll talk about kind of
our our what is this? The um the St.
Patty's Day free agency edition. We'll
do that after we do the brief.
>> Patty's Day.
>> Patty. Patty.
>> All right. Huddle up, team. It's time to
call a winter audible because when the
temps drop, the real magic kicks off in
West Virginia. Think trails that crunch
like game day turf. Ski runs for every
level of fan and cozy cabins that won't
break your budget. Trade lift line chaos
for wide open slopes, hot cocoa breaks
by crackling fires
>> by cocoa
>> and mountains dressed to impress in a
blanket purve white. So grab your squad,
pack your cold weather swag, and head to
almost heaven this winter, West
Virginia. Dude, that's like there's not
a better read in the game right now,
coach.
>> You can't act like it's the gospel.
>> I mean, that you Hey, you tell me. I
know you feel it. I know what he starts
talking about.
>> Cuz every TIME HE START DOING THE READ,
you look at me.
>> I'm just I'm just like, what? Like I'm
like, what are we over there doing?
Wiggling and wobbling. I'm like, what
are you over there talking about?
>> But I'm saying like but it's like what
are we going to do? Like I don't know
how you respond to that.
>> No, see when he put that old ass voice
on that that that's what it be with you.
Yeah, but I'm just like, "Oh, yeah. I'm
I'm Let's go."
>> Yeah. You get the chills and like, "Oh
my god, Reed Rainbow." Low
>> loud. All right, we got Geico.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, here we go. Fred, I mean, are
you nervous? Maybe a little bit.
>> L T were nervous. The doctor slapped me
on the back.
>> The le were nervous.
>> Oh, goodness gracious.
>> You know, isn't it strange? People
really want to save money, but are re
are so willing to toss their hard-earned
money into a threefoot pool of
disappointment. You don't need to throw
your money away. All you need is your
phone. Go to Geico, get a quote, and you
could save $900 with your phone. It
feels good to save some coin. It feels
good to Geico.
>> Great job. The funniest part of that is
when you tripped up and Jason's just in
the back.
>> KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING? THE PRESSURE IS SO
MUCH ON. I HATE TO SEE HOW Y'ALL DO
GUESS.
>> DUDE, JASON, MAN, that was
>> Jason has turned into a rotten guy.
>> I heard I heard Jason in the back, too.
I'm like,
>> hey, brought to you by Mississippi State
University. You know who does a good job
with the reads is
>> B Mitch. But be Mitch.
>> But B Mitch been doing radio reads the
whole time. I mean, his his experience
shows up big time.
>> No, no, but he been I've been say like
we going to give him no break. He been
reading he been reading for 10 years.
>> [__] and London. London. None of this
man.
>> You know what's crazy is like we had
this print for B Mitch. Yeah. He's like,
I can't read this. And Brian came back
with like I was like, Ryan, he can read.
It doesn't need to be like
>> the font was so big on that mother. The
fun the f I think B men had about 12
pages.
He had to He had
>> What about Blueoot?
>> I I mean Oh, dude. No, we're not going
to talk about that. We're not going to
talk about that.
>> What happened to Blue, man?
>> Ohio State University.
>> Leave Blue alone, man.
>> Yeah, that was a tough one. It was tough
for Ohio State that day. Okay, but he he
can bounce back. I believe that.
>> Well, Blue had he had a Sunny Styles
workout when he in the combine. We found
out Blue ran a 43.
>> That is pretty wild by Blue at like 200
lb, right?
>> Yeah. 20. All right, so now we got our
St. Patty's Day free agency recap. Gold
at the end of the rainbow and it's
brought to you by the US Army. Be
tested, but not just on paper. Be strong
and more than muscle. Be courageous and
supported by mighty team. Be all you can
be. Visit gormy.com to learn more. So,
we're going to go quick through these
because we have still another segment to
go because I've been slow on the on the
cover today. So,
>> yeah, you have.
>> Who would be your shamrock/4leaf
clover? someone you think um is the
diamond in the rough of this free agency
class.
>> I got Nick Cross.
>> Okay.
>> I got Nick Cross. I think he's a diamond
in the I think for the simple fact is
when you watch the caliber of play that
he displayed over there in uh
Indianapolis. Um defensively, man, one
of the things that sparked or or or
stood out to me is just the tackling
ability, being up close to the line of
scrimmage and being able to make those
plays. And then you think about our
safeties. you think about what we use
guys that play his position, how we can
be able to use him in certain packages
and being close up to the line of
scrimmage or being back there. Say to
me, I think he has a total package. I
also saw him, you know, be a great
defender. You know, PBU's at at a a huge
range of being able just to get his
hands on the ball. So, to me, when they
look at it, not might not be the the
flashy name, the sexiest one.
>> Yeah. Not not might not be the sexy
name, but to me, I think he one of those
sparkling diamonds. All you got to do is
do Hold on. polish that thing.
>> Polish that thing off a little bit and
now now it's going to glister a little
bit.
>> I would go I'm about to butcher his last
name. Charles
>> I'm out of here.
>> Oh, many of you.
>> Okay.
>> Well, let me tell you something.
>> Like coach said, I want winners.
>> I want winners.
>> He's a winner.
>> He's a winner. He's been there. He's
done that. All right. He's won
championships. He's been part of a
rotation. He knows how to be selfless.
And every time I see him playoff ball,
he seem to be getting a championship
ring. So maybe he is a fourleaf clover
in good luck. All right, cuz we got a
couple of ex- chiefs on this team. All
right, these guys come from Ren
instruction. So Charles is the fourleaf
clover to me.
>> I love it. So I'm going to go Leo Chanel
here. And I think because again, people
probably didn't know about him. He's
buried on the depth chart in Kansas City
with his teammate Charles Amenu. And I
just think he's
>> again like it's in there, man. First,
the utilization here is going to be a
big deal. Utilization. He's a Wisconsin
footballer. Oh, is he?
>> LIKE LIKE SOMETIME you tell me
>> you give me a call and say, "Hey, Fred,
I got this Wisconsin offensive lineman
for like
>> come on."
>> Like sometime I I just need to know
certain things and boy, he is the
epitome of what a Wisconsin linebacker
is. Most definitely downhill going to
put his face in the in in in the in the
blender.
>> All right, so next one. Yeah.
>> Who would be your pot of gold at the end
of the rainbow? basically like the
ultimate prize. You know, St. Patty's
Day, you're always hunting for that
gold, trying to catch a leprechaun, all
that stuff. Who would be the ultimate
prize
>> in this free agent class?
>> You want me to go first?
>> Yeah, you go first.
>> I'm going to cheat.
>> Can I cheat a little bit?
>> Yeah, you always do.
>> So, I'm going to say Laramie Tonsel.
Resigning here, I think, is a big one,
right? Like again, that wasn't cuz
technically under contract, so not a
free agent, but that was kind of looming
over the whole situation. And talk about
the big prize, like what are the most
important positions in football?
quarterback, edge rusher, left tackle.
Yeah. Right. And so to get that guy
under contract after he played last
year, after you traded for him, get that
all worked out and done. I think that is
the prize of the offseason.
>> Oh, Daly.
>> Oh, way.
>> All right. You know why?
>> I agree. I was going to go with the same
guy.
>> Yeah. Well, well, we can share him. All
right. 100 million reasons why we can
share him.
>> All right. You needed that point of
contact. When I say point of contact on
defense, it's always going to be this
guy that y'all y'all come out the
huddle. Where is he?
>> He's the guy.
>> He hasn't been that guy yet, but I think
he is going in that direction.
>> He's going in that direction. And if you
can, that guy opens it up for everybody
else.
>> Yeah, he remind me of when I'm watching
him. Um I remember playing against the
Dolphins and
>> Jace Taylor.
>> Jason Taylor. I remember being young in
high school or I can say that's I say
college when Jason Taylor was young.
>> Yeah.
>> And you heard so much about Zack Thomas.
Zack Thomas and then you just like who
the hell IS
>> WHO IS 99
>> cuz he keeps showing up
>> and then by the time I got to the league
Jordan had them signed in.
>> So
>> I'm just being real.
>> He just jumped off the screen and before
you know it was his defense. And I look
at this guy and I'm watching how he's a
first round draft pick. You know, he he
showed flashes last year. It took six
weeks, but then he end up getting traded
and then it said to the and out of
nowhere just boom, he here.
>> Yeah.
>> Guys like that showing you that he
hasn't reached his peak yet. He has he
hasn't he hasn't plateaued yet. You see
what I'm saying? So I feel like he has
the capability of really jumping off the
screen cuz he really just getting
started.
>> Just scratching the surface. just
scratching the surface.
>> Yeah, totally agree with that. And
again, I think he he was used as that
one guy like at points last year, but I
think he's just ready for like that full
>> he want it all right now. And then you
got other guys too cuz I think and like
I'm saying, I'm not trying to jump the
gun and know how the road is going to
be,
>> how they going to use him, but you have
other guys that you can always say like
I don't have to have him out there in
downs where I don't think he can be
effective. You know what I mean? Not to
say they won't, but I'm just saying like
you'll be able to use this guy. Say,
"Hey, maybe we can move him around and
and get some of these match up favorable
matchups or something like that."
>> All right. So, who would you consider to
be the leprechaun of this class? So,
kind of like maybe someone that's like
the the road isn't clear, a little
sneaky, mischievous, kind of a I don't
want to say under the radar signing, but
like someone you think is going to do
this big impact.
>> Yeah. I'm going with the Robinson Meek
Meek Robinson.
>> Oh, I like that one. I just feel like,
man, you know,
>> I want I want a I want a guy that's
gonna be competitive at corner.
>> I want competition fighter.
>> I need a I need a guy that look here.
>> I don't have to be the best of the best
that the people see or talk about all
the time, but every time you line up in
front of me, I'm bringing my hard hat
and my lunch puff sled for you. Yeah,
>> I told you when I played against guys, I
probably had my better days against the
name guys. It was the guys I didn't know
that gave me a hard time and also the
guys that had a great front.
>> We look like we going to have a great
front. When you have a great front and
you get scrappy guys like a Meek
Robinson, it's going to be a long day
for you. We saw Jefferson have to go
against him when he was over there in
Detroit a few times and it was tough
sledding for him. So that's what I want.
I want a guy that's going to be highly
competitive every down. going to give
you everything he got and it's going to
be hard for you to go out there and have
a productive day on. I'm going get
cheeky with it,
>> dude. I was going to say I'm get chicky
with it. That's what I'm
>> That's a good one.
>> I was going to say I was going to say
like that, but yeah, I say we get cheeky
with it. And that's who I think it is. I
just think
>> because most people don't know how to
say his name.
>> Yeah,
>> they won't pick him. But I just think
that vow for JD5
>> dumping it off. I can see right now the
play breaking down. JD5 running out
getting outside of the pocket. Chig
started running a a a five yard out
router. He done broke that thing up.
Before we know it, he done lost it up
and ran away from somebody. So, I'm
going to go Chiggy with it. I'm going to
stay right there.
>> Yeah, I totally agree with the Chig
thing. To me, it's also like how do you
use him? Talk about like a joker kind of
funny piece for the offense. Like
>> he could play he could get carries out
of the back field.
>> No, no. Very much like January.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Very similar. I like that
comp actually quite a bit. But like he
could do whatever you need him to do.
Screens, yards have to catch stuff. Like
>> what's he going to be in this and he
could be really special. So looking
forward to that. All right, let's get to
this third break, pay some bills, and
then we've got draft strategy changes
after free agency after that. But
>> well, Young,
>> in the meantime, we got Virginia
Lottery. Who's got this one?
>> I think I I was toting it for a while.
>> Toting it. Huddle up, Commanders fans.
The Commander Golden Pass Raffle
operated by the Virginia Lottery gives
you a chance to win the ultimate fan
experience. That means tickets, VIP
treatment, special appearances by
Washington Legends like us guys, and
much more. Limited tickets available.
So, visit valottery.com/commanders
to enter the raffle today. That's
valottery.com/commanders
and break.
>> Well done. I was thinking about Jason
laughing while you were
>> I don't worry about Jason. You see this
funny the go.
>> It was pretty funny. It's good little
time.
>> All right.
>> They say your work defines who you are.
Monday through Friday 9 to 5 you're
clocking in. But what happens on the
weekend? What happens to your time? You
could take it easy or you could use that
time to get better. In the US Army we
think differently. Your time should be
used to improve the skills you do have
to learn something you don't to push
yourself in new ways. Because it's those
days that truly define who you are.
That's how you make progress. That's how
you make an impact on the world around
you. It's your time. How you spend it's
up to you. It's your time. The US Army
Reserve
>> about to join.
>> Boy, please.
>> All right. So, we teased it. How does
this whole free agent thing? We talked
about, you know,
>> you know, how it started, how it's
going, guys. We like all this stuff. How
does it change the draft strategy? We're
going to rip through this cuz we're over
an hour and you guys got better things
to do than listen to us all day. Um,
okay. So, now that the roster is filling
out in free agency, right? We're not
done yet. Still some other signings to
do, but we see the big pieces.
>> How does the draft strategy change for
AP?
>> I I think it just made it wide open. I
just think
>> talk about that because I don't think I
I agree with you. Yeah.
>> But like elaborate on like what that
means.
>> We went into free agency with a lot of
questions, a lot of hoes. We left free
agencies with a lot of questions
answered. You ask me where the pass
rush, I can show you four or five
different guys. You ask me about a
defensive back, we got a Meek. You want
to ask me about bringing Larry Matonsel
back so we don't have to fill that gap.
Uh we we we packed the running back
room, right? We added a wide receiver.
So now he's making it till when I say
cuz a lot of people when they hear best
player available,
>> they don't actually know what that
means.
>> You have to have the luxury to be able
to take best player available. Cuz the
worst thing I always tell people you
want to do in the draft is, "All right,
we're going into this draft. We need a
first round offensive lineman. We going
to be forced to take whatever offensive
linement follow to us because that's
where the hole at." No, that ain't how
people build winning teams. You build
winning teams through optimism.
>> And you can only be optimism, have
optimism if you have options.
>> Yeah,
>> we have options now to literally
>> do we need Jeremiah Love in that room?
It would be a luxury. Yeah.
>> All right. Do we need Sunny Styles in
the linebacker room? Nope. But it would
be a luxury. So it if everything comes
off as a luxury, you had to do something
before the draft to get to this point.
>> Let me see how can I put this in a not
so harsh way.
>> Oh god.
>> Already giving you a tea up. Jason,
>> are you going to
>> It's like that guy, right? Uhoh. This
should go down. This could go either
way.
>> Yeah. We don't know where we're going.
>> We're hanging on for dear life.
>> You always wonder why when I go into
that diner,
he got that toothpick in his mouth and
he just reading that paper. What do he
do for a living?
>> He got all his jewelry on. He got a nice
car.
And he say
fold that paper say I'mma see you
tomorrow. Cuz he got workers.
>> He don't do no work. He ain't got to
work.
>> So when I look at AP, that's what AP
doing. He going to fold up his he going
to fold his paper up and he going to
say, "I got workers." Now, who we go out
there and get to add to them?
>> Mhm.
>> It's up to us.
>> Yeah.
>> Because like you just said, it's the
best guy available. And what folks fail
to realize, the worst thing to do is to
go in the draft and say, "We desperate
for this position."
>> For this position.
>> We're desperate.
>> Cuz it'll make you like somebody that
ain't good.
>> Look, you're gonna That's true. talking
about moving a guy up who was a second
round potential to first because that's
where we pick at and we need a guy.
>> We ain't got to do that. Yeah. We going
to get the best available because guess
what? Whoever we bring to the table, all
you're doing is making us better. Yeah.
>> You just making my work, you know,
>> but not a necessity.
>> But not a necessity. And and my thing is
just to be more I'm going to get off
that a little bit.
>> We have it. We have whatever you want to
call it in our hands. Like we control it
right now. It don't. We don't have to
necessarily say, "I'm going after Love
because Love is the best running back
and I have to get a running back." We
don't have that.
>> I'm going after Bailey because guess
what? He's the best pass rusher. We have
that.
>> Now, if one of those guys are there and
we sitting there to us,
>> we can go get who we want, when we want.
So, I just feel like we're in a great
situation. And that's
>> that's a situation I haven't seen our
team in in a long time. You know what I
mean? for many years when we played.
I've seen us go pick guys and I was
scratching my head
>> when we picked him and when we was in
practice with him.
>> Yeah.
>> Like
>> I been ain't know why you was here.
>> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> So at the end of the day, I just feel
like we in a situation where we don't
have to work go out there and stress
oursel with going to find somebody. If
somebody fall there, we'll pick them.
>> We want volunteers, not hostage.
>> You maybe answered this question
already, but is there a position you
would or wouldn't stress um at seven?
You know what I'm saying? like you know
is like like oh now we're good we
wouldn't draft this guy or now we have
to kind of think this way
>> I think we scratched it all
>> so let me so I got two spots for you one
is running back right again we're fine
>> but like
>> getting a playmaking piece there would
be
>> you saying a x factor
>> yes and then also receiver it seems like
we're fine but getting that guy under
contract opposite Terry
>> also seems like a nice idea too so like
I'm not saying we like
>> but can I ask you something? Yeah, go
ahead.
>> For the receivers that's in this draft
>> is seven
too high for these guys.
>> So that's that's what I wanted to ask
you about. And again, I like Carnell
Tate. I like Jordan Tyson. I like Lemon
a lot.
>> I don't know if I like him. Sell them.
>> That's what I'm saying. So So but but
but when you said, are you are you
looking at something and valuing it more
because you feel like you need it? No.
>> Like that's that's that's my thing
there. Because if if it was a Jace in
this draft,
>> Jamar Chase,
>> Jamar Chase in this draft,
>> I ain't no hesitation.
>> I just don't feel like it's one of those
in this draft.
>> I agree.
>> So, I feel like if I take
>> But it's kind of a funny draft, too.
Like, because there's not like a ton of
like blue chip guys. So, can you just be
like, "Hey, we we think, you know, the
receiver is the same as the as the uh as
the safety or the corner or the
offensive lineman, and we like this guy
the better." I look at I look at say if
say for instance you do get a Tate if
Tate is the is if if if he's projected
to be the first receiver I won't
hesitate from if he's available and I I
don't have the other guys that who I got
in front of him on my chart.
>> Yeah.
>> I won't look at it being odd that I
would pick him at seven. But I feel like
his his play showed that kind of a
>> it's just first round is a first round.
>> He's a first round. Like I I don't care
where up and down that first line. He's
a first round talent. When I say this,
Logan, if I had to choose between
Cardell Tate and Caleb DS
>> at seven,
>> I'm taking Tate.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm surprised by that, actually.
>> Well, I I told you as much as I like DS.
>> What's his freakish trait?
>> Yeah. You said this earlier and this is
an interesting So, I've always been kind
of doing the money thing with the
receiver. Like, receivers are going to
like next year in free agency, like
Drake London, I think, is going to
probably make $32 million.
>> 35.
>> Yeah. So, if you sign a receiver, you
draft a receiver, you're saving yourself
10 to 12 million bucks, which is a good
football player.
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
>> DS obviously the money like he'll be
played like a top five safety right out
the gate, which is
>> but the film for DS I think is better,
but you you're in on this trait thing
which I think is a good point. Yeah. Can
you elaborate on that?
>> Well, when I say elite trait, like the
one thing about it is when when I say
Sunny Styles, the first thing that jump
out of he's just his athletic profile as
a linebacker is just unbelievable. Uh
RVL Reese, you like, "Oh my god, David
Bailey."
>> Yeah. Like Jeremiah Love.
>> Jeremiah Love got these freakish traits.
>> Well, Caleb is just he just checks all
the boxes.
>> Good.
>> I mean, the film the film is excellent,
but the other stuff he hasn't done yet.
He hasn't run yet.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> So, so it's just one of these things. He
ain't Shawn Taylor to me, right?
>> You see what I'm saying? That's
>> fair. That's the only thing I'm saying
like it it's a different level of of of
freaky athlete and I just don't think
he's that.
>> That's a good point. And so, if you want
more kind of that of that kind of draft
analysis, make sure you check out Drive
of the Draft. We do a ton of that work
on there. But I to me it's like we're
not stressed at anybody, but I wonder if
there's
>> parts that feel a little bit weaker
where maybe we go with seven. That's my
only thought there. Okay, this is maybe
the most interesting question. It's the
last one and we're going to do it quick
because I don't think it needs that much
analysis, but it's really interesting.
On a scale of 1 to 10, how comfortable
are you trading back from seven now? I'm
going to go first in terms of comfort.
>> Yeah,
>> I'm a 10 out of 10.
>> Yeah.
>> Trade back.
>> Yeah, I'm totally comfort.
>> But
who wants it? Like somebody got to want
to
>> like like All right. Do you think it
could be a late late Tai Simpson run?
Aita. Uh,
>> so I heard I heard something I heard
something crazy today. Heard something
crazy today. Okay.
>> If Jeremiah loves at seven and let's say
the Cleveland Browns want to trade 24
with you and they're going to give you
24, 39, and 70 in this year's draft.
>> Oh yeah, I'm I'm giving it to the paper.
Let me sign.
>> Yeah, give it a go. Right. It just
depends on who and what, right? who's
going to trade up from where and who who
do they want to get there. Yeah, because
there's
>> it's kind of a funny draft that way,
right? So, like that's
>> but we see it every year. The
quarterbacks, they they always make a
run.
>> If Tai Simpson like right now, I just
talking to Jason about this
>> and producer Amanda like I want Tai
Simpson to have the best pre-draft
process possible. I want people be like,
"Man, this guy is amazing.
>> He's a coach. He's fantastic. Killing
the interview." Ty Simpson cuz I want
someone to be like, "Man, we got to
draft that dude." Yeah. And they're
gonna trade up with Washington. Yes. And
make an irrational decision.
>> Totally irrational.
>> He should not go. He should not go at
seven.
>> Ty Simpson is is is 13 inches tall. I'm
telling you, we've seen this story
before. We've seen the Ty de We've seen
this story before and it always happened
at a school like Alabama.
>> I love I love the trade back just for
the simple fact of you know, you know
how we say less is more at times. No,
not in this situation. We need more. You
know what I mean? It's a must. But at
the same time, like I say, we don't have
to worry about it. If it's there, if
it's available for us to get more, we
get it. If not, then all right.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, dude, that was a heck of a
show. You guys did a great job.
Fantastic work. I think
>> I think I'd give the arrow to Santana
here as the read.
>> I give it a Fred.
>> Would you That's way too much humility.
>> Leonardo Gotress is what I go by.
>> I give I give it.
>> So, but make sure you vote on that in
the comments.
>> I let them do the probably in the
meantime.
>> Welcome back, Fred.
>> That's it. The Command Center podcast
was filmed at the Big Bear AI command
center studio. Big Bear AI offers
mission ready AI for a rapidly evolving
world, proudly protecting the Washington
Commanders and its fans.